bindaasbargain.com 2011-06-09

# BindaasBargain.com Our Policies

#### 

Privacy Policy

Bindaas Bargain and its affiliates respect the privacy of your personal information. This Privacy Policy incorporates the details of the data that is collected and used by Bindaas Bargain. You are advised to read the Privacy Policy carefully. By using the website [www.BindaasBargain.com](http://www.bindaasbargain.com/) and by accessing the services provided by Bindaas Bargain you agree to the collection and use of your data by Bindaas Bargain in the manner provided in this Privacy Policy.

The purpose of publishing this document is to inform you in detail about the collection and usage of your information by Bindaas Bargain so you feel comfortable in using our website and also ask us questions if you have any concerns about the use of this data.

**What information is, or may be, collected from you?**  

We will automatically receive and collect certain anonymous information in standard usage logs through our Web server, including computer-identification information obtained from "cookies," sent to your browser from a

  * web server cookie stored on your hard drive
  * an IP address, assigned to the computer which you use
  * the domain server through which you access our service
  * the type of computer you're using
  * the type of web browser you're using 

We may collect the following personally identifiable information about you:

  * name including first and last name 
  * email address 
  * mobile phone number and contact details 
  * PIN/Postal code
  * financial information (like account or credit card numbers); and
  * Opinions on features on our websites. 
  * Other information as per our registration process 
  * Comments / opinions expressed by you either on our ‘Disscussions’ page, ‘Write to us’ page, or Bindaas Bargain fan page on Facebook.

We may also collect the following information:

  * about the pages you visit/access
  * the links you click on our site 
  * the number of times you access the page 
  * the number of times you visit our web site 
  * the items purchased by you on our website

You can stop using your account at our web site at any time. However, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or the termination of your account.

We will collect anonymous traffic information from you when you visit our site. We will collect personally identifiable information about you only as part of a voluntary registration process, on-line survey, or contest or any combination thereof.

**How is the information used?**

We use your personal information to:

  * help us provide personalized features to you
  * tailor our site to your interest 
  * to get in touch with you when necessary
  * to keep you informed about our daily or other offers via email and/or sms alerts. You have a right to opt-out of getting the daily email and/or sms alerts.
  * to provide the services (purchases, refunds, replacements, shipping, etc.) requested by you 
  * to preserve history of your interactions with Bindaas Bargain, as governed by existing law or policy 

We use contact information internally to:

  * direct our efforts for product improvement 
  * contact you as a survey respondent 
  * notify you if you win any contest; and 
  * send you promotional materials from our contest sponsors or advertisers 

Generally, we use anonymous traffic information to:

  * remind us of who you are in order to deliver to you a better and more personalized service from both an advertising and an editorial perspective; 
  * recognize your access privileges to our Websites 
  * track your entries in some of our promotions and contests to indicate a user's progress through the promotion and to track entries, submissions, and status in prize drawings 
  * help diagnose problems with our server 
  * administer our website, track your session so that we can understand better how people use our sites 

We use the Comments / Opinions expressed by you to:

  * show them to other visitors to our website so they can  use the information in any way they want
  * display your comment / opinion anywhere on our website or on any promotional material (including Bindaas Bargain fan page on Facebook, magazine articles, newspaper articles, marketing material prepared by Bindaas Bargain, etc.) 

We use your purchase information to:

Offer you relevant products for purchase based on average user purchase behavior.

Show it to other visitors on the website to help them make a decision about the purchase.

**With whom will your information be shared?**  

We will not use your financial information for any purpose other than to complete a transaction with you. 

We do not rent, sell or share your personal information and we will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information to third parties unless:

  * we have your permission 
  * to provide products or services you've requested 
  * to help investigate, prevent or take action regarding unlawful and illegal activities, suspected fraud, potential threat to the safety or security of any person, violations of Bindaas Bargain's terms of use or to defend against legal claims 
  * Special circumstances such as compliance with subpoenas, court orders, requests/order, notices from legal authorities or law enforcement agencies requiring such disclosure 

We share your information with advertisers on an aggregate basis only.   

You may change your interests at any time and may opt-in or opt-out of any marketing / promotional / newsletters mailings. Bindaas Bargain reserves the right to send you certain service related communication, considered to be a part of your Bindaas Bargain account without offering you the facility to opt-out. You may update your information and change your account settings at any time. 

Upon request, we will remove/block your personally identifiable information from our database, thereby disabling your registration. However, your information may remain stored on our servers even after the disabling of your account. 

If we plan to use your personally identifiable information for any commercial purposes, we will notify you at the time we collect that information and allow you to opt-out of having your information used for those purposes.

**What security procedures are in place to protect information from loss, misuse or alteration?**  

To protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, we have in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures. For example, our servers are accessible only to authorized personnel and that your information is shared with respective personnel on need to know basis to complete the transaction and to provide the services requested by you. 

Although we will endeavor to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. By using this site, you agree that we will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties.

**Policy updates**  

We reserve the right to change or update this policy at any time by placing a prominent notice on our site. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting to this site.

#### 

Shipping Policy

**Bindaas Bargain is committed to deliver your order accurately, in good condition and always on time.**

Please note our shipping policy: 

  * We currently deliver to more than 1500 cities across India. Click here to check the PIN codes we deliver to. 
  * We ship Monday through Saturday, except on public holidays.
  * To ensure that your order reaches you in good condition, in the shortest span of time, we ship through premier courier agencies only. 
  * If you deem the product to be in a bad condition or if the packaging is tampered with or damaged before delivery, please refuse to accept the package. Call our customer care at (120) 4098888 or email us at [connect@bindaasbargain.com](mailto:connect@bindaasbargain.com), mentioning your Order ID. We will ensure that a replacement delivery is made to you at the earliest. 

#### 

Product Refund/Return Policy

We are committed to ensuring your satisfaction with any product that you have ordered from BindaasBargain.com. However, if in an unlikely event you are not satisfied with your purchase, BindaasBargain.com follows the below mentioned Refund/Return Policy: 

**Damaged/Tampered Delivery**

Please do not accept the delivery of any item from the courier/delivery person, if you feel that the outer packaging is Damaged/Tampered. Please contact our customer care for replacement, immediately. 

**Damaged/Defective Product**

In an unlikely event, if the product you received from us is damaged/defective, please call the customer care within 3 working days for a refund/replacement.  
Products damaged while being used, do not qualify for refund/replacement. In case we are unable to replace the damaged/defective product, we will refund your money. 

**15-day money back policy**

If you change your mind about the purchase and haven’t opened the package as yet, you can call us within 15 days of ordering the product. We will refund your money deducting only 10% of the product cost incurred in packaging and handling. 

**Returning the product**

For initiating the return of a product, you may contact our customer care and request a return/replacement. We will arrange for the products to be collected from the delivery address through courier and shall process the return/replacement subject to receipt of the product(s) at our location in unused condition and in its original packaging, failing which return/replacement may not be possible. At the time of collecting the product(s), you will be given a courier Airway Bill, which is to be retained for future reference. 

**Refund**

  * If the payment was by Credit Card / NetBanking / Debit Card, we will refund your Credit Card / NetBanking / Debit Card account respectively. 
  * If the payment was by Cash On Delivery / Cash Before Delivery, we will refund your money via a cheque written in your name. You will have to provide the following details:  
Your name (as on your bank account)  
Order ID 
  * The refund process will be initiated once we have received the product(s). Typically refunds are processed in less than 10 working days but in case of payments by Cash On Delivery and Cash Before Delivery, it may take a few extra days for the cheque to be delivered to your billing address and for the funds to be credited to your account, once you deposit the cheque. 
  * Please note that we shall not be responsible for any delays in credit to the cardholder's Credit Card / NetBanking / Debit Card account as that is managed by the Cardholder's issuing bank. 

If you have any questions to ask, any doubts to clarify, any complaints to make, do contact us via phone or email. 

Call our customer care at + (91) (120) 409 8888 or email us at [connect@bindaasbargain.com](mailto:connect@bindaasbargain.com)  
We will respond to your query within a few hours during work days (Mon - Sat: 10:30 am - 6:30 pm). 

#### 

Bindaas Bargain Discussions Section (Wall) Policy

Bindaas Bargain does not moderate/delete any comments and welcomes all types of suggestions and ideas whether supportive, dissenting, critical or otherwise on the Bindaas Wall with the exception of: 

  * Comments containing profanities or racist / discriminatory items. 
  * Non-constructive hateful or spiteful comments. 
  * Recurring, disruptive personal attacks. 
  * Advertisement / promotion of personal interest / business by users. 
  * Comments that are blatantly spam. 
  * We retain the right to moderate/delete any comments if any one user posts more than three comments in a day. The wall is intended for unbiased and impartial discussions among the Bindaas community, but if one user starts to dominate the discussion, that impacts the purpose of the wall adversely. 

For the above mentioned cases, Bindaas Bargain reserves the right to moderate or delete the same. 

Go Bindaas!  
Team Bindaas Bargain
